Register of the Oleg Ivanovich Pantiukhov papers
Hoover Institution Archives
- Correspondence, 1912-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 4-14 (Reel 5-23)
  - Koshlakov, M., Rev., 1972; Box/Folder 9: 16 (Reel 14)
  - Kosorotov, D., 1969; Box/Folder 9: 17 (Reel 14)
  - Koval'kov, N. and N., 1932-1967; Box/Folder 9: 18 (Reel 14)
  - Koval'skii de Shmiden, A., 1967-1972 and undated; Box/Folder 9: 19 (Reel 14)
  - Koverda, N., 1969; Box/Folder 9: 20 (Reel 14)
  - Kozintsova-Durnovo, V. A., 1947 and undated; Box/Folder 9: 21 (Reel 14)
  - Kozlov, L. N., 1961-1969; Box/Folder 9: 22 (Reel 14)
  - Krasovskii, Vadim, 1958-1973
    - 1958-1969 and undated, Box/Folder 9: 23 (Reel 14)
    - 1970-1973, Box/Folder 9: 24 (Reel 14)
  - Kravtsevich, Natal'ia Dmitrievna, undated; Box/Folder 10: 1 (Reel 15)
  - Krushinskaia, Z., 1946; Box/Folder 10: 2 (Reel 15)
  - Kudasheva, S., 1923; Box/Folder 10: 3 (Reel 15)
  - Kudrik, Petr, 1962; Box/Folder 10: 4 (Reel 15)
  - Kulikovskii, Tikhon N., 1972; Box/Folder 10: 5 (Reel 15)
  - Kutukov, Leonid, 1967-1969; Box/Folder 10: 6 (Reel 15)
  - Kutyrina, Iuliia, 1968-1969; Box/Folder 10: 7 (Reel 15)
  - Kvinitadze, G., 1968; Box/Folder 10: 8 (Reel 15)
  - Lampe, Aleksei Aleksandovich von, 1960-1962; Box/Folder 10: 9 (Reel 15)
  - Langer, Georgii, 1962-1968; Box/Folder 10: 10 (Reel 15)
  - Laskin-Rostovskii, Iu., 1968 and undated; Box/Folder 10: 11 (Reel 15)
  - Leidenius, V. N., Dr., 1946-1952; Box/Folder 10: 12 (Reel 15)
  - Leontii, Bishop, 1929-1936; Box/Folder 10: 13 (Reel 15)
  - Levitskii, Oleg E., 1958-1973; Box/Folder 10: 14 (Reel 15)
  - Life Magazine, 1939; Box/Folder 10: 15 (Reel 15)
  - Lipskii, Aleksandr Fedorovich, 1924; Box/Folder 10: 16 (Reel 15)
  - Losev, Viktor, 1968; Box/Folder 10: 17 (Reel 15)
  - Loviagin, Roman Mikhailovich, undated; Box/Folder 10: 18 (Reel 15)
  - Liubomirov, Nikolai Ivanovich, 1971; Box/Folder 10: 19 (Reel 15)
  - Lukash, Ivan, 1938; Box/Folder 10: 20 (Reel 15)
  - Lukashkin, Anatolii Stefanovich, 1954-1959; Box/Folder 10: 21 (Reel 15)
  - Lukin, Georgii, 1936-1971.; Box/Folder 10: 22 (Reel 15)
    Includes materials about him and third-party correspondence
  - L'vova, V., 1966-1969; Box/Folder 10: 23 (Reel 15)
  - Maevskii, V., 1966; Box/Folder 10: 24 (Reel 15)
  - Maish, Vadim, 1922-1927; Box/Folder 10: 25 (Reel 15)
  - Maksimov, Vissarion, 1972; Box/Folder 10: 26 (Reel 15)
  - Mamontova, E., 1950; Box/Folder 10: 27 (Reel 15)
  - Martino, Boris Borisovich, 1948; Box/Folder 10: 28 (Reel 15)
  - Martynov, Mr., 1935(?); Box/Folder 10: 29 (Reel 15)
  - Matsylev, S., 1935; Box/Folder 10: 30 (Reel 15)
  - Meer, Olga, 1950; Box/Folder 10: 31 (Reel 15)
  - Mende, E., undated; Box/Folder 10: 32 (Reel 15)
  - Mering, Sofiia Sergeevna, 1949 and undated; Box/Folder 10: 33 (Reel 15)
  - Mers'e, Vladimir V., 1959-1972; Box/Folder 10: 34 (Reel 15)
  - Miagkov, R., 1967-1972; Box/Folder 10: 35 (Reel 15)
  - Mikhalevskii, Sergei Nikolaevich, 1969; Box/Folder 10: 36 (Reel 15)
  - Mikhailov, Nikolai Petrovich, 1958; Box/Folder 10: 37 (Reel 15)
  - Mikhal'skii, Andrei Nikolaevich, 1950-1967; Box/Folder 10: 38 (Reel 15)
  - Mikhieev, Leonid M., 1949; Box/Folder 10: 39 (Reel 15)
  - Mikhonskii, Andrei, 1951-1969; Box/Folder 10: 40 (Reel 15)
  - Miller, Evgenii Karlovich and N., 1928-1936; Box/Folder 10: 41 (Reel 15)
  - Mironovich, Pavel Ignat'evich, 1972; Box/Folder 10: 42 (Reel 15)
  - Mittelstaedt, Eduard, 1947-1961; Box/Folder 10: 43 (Reel 15)
  - Mogilat, Elena, 1969; Box/Folder 10: 44 (Reel 15)
  - Morozevich, Aleksandr E., 1971; Box/Folder 10: 45 (Reel 15)
  - Morozov, Nikolai, 1959-1969; Box/Folder 10: 46 (Reel 15)
  - Mozhaiskaia, Ol'ga, 1967-1969; Box/Folder 10: 47 (Reel 15)
  - Mozhaiskii, A. A., 1967-1972; Box/Folder 10: 48 (Reel 15)
  - Mozhaiskii, Aleksei N., 1966-1971; Box/Folder 11: 1 (Reel 16)
  - Mul'tanen-Sakharov, L., 1958-1972; Box/Folder 11: 2 (Reel 16)
  - Mysiakov, Nikolai Nikolaevich, 1961; Box/Folder 11: 3 (Reel 16)
  - Nazanskii, N., 1929-1931; Box/Folder 11: 4 (Reel 16)
  - Nechaev, V., 1969 and undated; Box/Folder 11: 5 (Reel 16)
  - Nektarii, Bishop, 1971 and undated; Box/Folder 11: 6 (Reel 16)
  - Nervana, Pavel, 1945; Box/Folder 11: 7 (Reel 16)
  - Nestor, Bishop, 1927; Box/Folder 11: 8 (Reel 16)
  - Nevzorov, A., 1968; Box/Folder 11: 9 (Reel 16)
  - Nikolaev, Mikhail Vital'evich, 1956-1972; Box/Folder 11: 10 (Reel 16)
  - Nikolai Nikolaevich, Grand Duke, 1925-1928; Box/Folder 11: 11 (Reel 16)
  - Nikon, Bishop, 1948-1973; Box/Folder 11: 12 (Reel 16)
  - Novitskii, I., 1930; Box/Folder 11: 13 (Reel 16)
  - Novoe russkoe slovo, 1969; Box/Folder 11: 14 (Reel 16)
  - Ob"edinenie kirasir Eia Velichestva, 1970; Box/Folder 11: 15 (Reel 16)
  - Ob"edinenie tiflisstsev, 1937; Box/Folder 11: 16 (Reel 16)
  - Obshchestvo okhraneniia russkikh kul'turnykh tsiennostei, 1961; Box/Folder 11: 17 (Reel 16)
  - Odinets, Mikhail Dmitrievich, 1955-1972; Box/Folder 11: 18 (Reel 16)
  - Okhotnikov, Aleksandr, 1972 and undated; Box/Folder 11: 19 (Reel 16)
  - Okulich, Vladimir, 1927-1929; Box/Folder 11: 20 (Reel 16)
  - Onoshkovich-Iatsyna, L., 1968-1969; Box/Folder 11: 21 (Reel 16)
  - Orekhov, Vasilii V., 1948-1955; Box/Folder 11: 22 (Reel 16)
  - Orlova, E., 1963-1972; Box/Folder 11: 23 (Reel 16)
  - Pantiukhova, M., 1948-1949; Box/Folder 11: 24 (Reel 16)
  - Perott, B. A., 1934-1948; Box/Folder 11: 25 (Reel 16)
  - Perov, L., 1968; Box/Folder 11: 26 (Reel 16)
  - Pertsov, Konstantin Aleksandrovich, 1923-1970; Box/Folder 11: 27 (Reel 16)
  - Pertsova, Ol'ga, 1938; Box/Folder 11: 28 (Reel 16)
  - Petrov, N. V., 1926; Box/Folder 11: 29 (Reel 16)
  - Petrushevskii, Vladimir Aleksandrovich, 1959; Box/Folder 11: 30 (Reel 16)
  - Pianovskii, L., 1966; Box/Folder 11: 31 (Reel 16)
  - Pigarev, V. V., 1959; Box/Folder 11: 32 (Reel 16)
  - Pisareva, V., 1960-1970 and undated; Box/Folder 11: 33 (Reel 16)
  - Piterskii, Evgenii Sergeevich, 1961-1972; Box/Folder 11: 34 (Reel 16)
  - Plekhanov, Mikhail M., 1935-1972 and undated; Box/Folder 11: 35 (Reel 17)
  - Pogozheva, Aleksandra S., undated; Box/Folder 12: 1 (Reel 17)
  - Pokrovskaia, Irina Sergeevna, 1923-1965; Box/Folder 12: 2 (Reel 17)
  - Polchaninov, Rostislav Vladimirovich, 1938-1972; Box/Folder 12: 3 (Reel 17)
  - Poliakov, V., 1954-1956; Box/Folder 12: 4 (Reel 17)
  - Pol'skii, Mikhail, Rev., 1966; Box/Folder 12: 5 (Reel 17)
  - Pomerantsev, K., 1967-1969; Box/Folder 12: 6 (Reel 17)
  - Ponomarev, Andrei, 1939-1946; Box/Folder 12: 7 (Reel 17)
  - Popov, Igor Vsevolodovich, 1967-1968; Box/Folder 12: 8 (Reel 17)
  - Popov, S., 1946-1949; Box/Folder 12: 9 (Reel 17)
  - Potemkin, Nikolai Aleksandrovich, 1929; Box/Folder 12: 10 (Reel 17)
  - Pozdieev, Evgenii Evgenievich, 1966; Box/Folder 12: 11 (Reel 17)
  - Pram, Ivan and Ol'ga, 1949-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 12 (Reel 17)
  - Prokop'ev, Viktor, 1928; Box/Folder 12: 13 (Reel 17)
  - Pushchin, Oleg, 1947; Box/Folder 12: 14 (Reel 17)
  - Pushkarev, Boris Sergeevich, 1953; Box/Folder 12: 15 (Reel 17)
  - Rachinskaia, N., undated; Box/Folder 12: 16 (Reel 17)
  - Rachinskii, Konstantin Konstantinovich, 1929; Box/Folder 12: 17 (Reel 17)
  - Radchenko, Irina, 1969; Box/Folder 12: 18 (Reel 17)
  - Radetskii-Mikulich, 1949-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 19 (Reel 17)
  - Ravera, Nina, 1969-1972; Box/Folder 12: 20 (Reel 18)
  - Razsadin, Georgii, 1958-1963 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 21 (Reel 18)
  - Razvozova, M., undated; Box/Folder 12: 22 (Reel 18)
  - Reingard, Konstantin Fedorovich, 1968-1969; Box/Folder 12: 23 (Reel 18)
  - Rezaeva, I., 1959-1973; Box/Folder 12: 24 (Reel 18)
  - Ross, G., 1967-1970; Box/Folder 12: 25 (Reel 18)
  - Rostovzeff, Michael, 1944; Box/Folder 12: 26 (Reel 18)
  - Rozenberg, Vladimir Vladimirovich, 1950-1951 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 27 (Reel 18)
  - Rozenshil'd-Paulin, A., 1929; Box/Folder 12: 28 (Reel 18)
  - Rudnev, V., 1924-1959; Box/Folder 12: 29 (Reel 18)
  - Rulle, Antoinette, 1948 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 30 (Reel 18)
  - Safonov, 1962; Box/Folder 12: 31 (Reel 18)
  - Saint Herman of Alaska Brotherhood, 1972; Box/Folder 12: 32 (Reel 18)
  - Sakhnovskii, A. and N., 1947-1967; Box/Folder 12: 33 (Reel 18)
  - Satterlee, M., 1971; Box/Folder 12: 34 (Reel 18)
  - Savva, Archbishop, 1959; Box/Folder 12: 35 (Reel 18)
  - Sedliarevich, Nikolai Mikhailovich, 1930-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 36 (Reel 18)
  - Selivanovskii, Vsevolod, 1950-1969 and undated; Box/Folder 12: 37 (Reel 18)
  - Semenov, Grigorii M., 1939; Box/Folder 13: 1 (Reel 18)
  - Semov, Innokentii Ivanovich, 1937; Box/Folder 13: 2 (Reel 18)
  - Serafim, Archbishop, 1972; Box/Folder 13: 3 (Reel 18)
  - Seregin, Aleksandr, 1955; Box/Folder 13: 4 (Reel 18)
  - Sergievskii, Boris, 1930; Box/Folder 13: 5 (Reel 18)
  - Shakhovskaia, Zinaida, 1968-1969 and undated; Box/Folder 13: 6 (Reel 18)
  - Shaternik, A., 1934-1935; Box/Folder 13: 7 (Reel 18)
  - Shchupliak, Elena Vladimirovna, 1967-1969; Box/Folder 13: 8 (Reel 19)
  - Shemetillo, 1939; Box/Folder 13: 9 (Reel 19)
  - Shirinkin, Evgenii Evgenievich, 1969; Box/Folder 13: 10 (Reel 19)
    Includes photograph
  - Shmitov, Igor', 1949-1951; Box/Folder 13: 11 (Reel 19)
  - Shnitnikova, Liudmila, 1969; Box/Folder 13: 12 (Reel 19)
  - Shostakovich, Valerii Aleksandrovich, 1964-1969; Box/Folder 13: 13 (Reel 19)
  - Shtakel'berg, Tat'iana, 1940-1969; Box/Folder 13: 14 (Reel 19)
  - Shtal', K., undated; Box/Folder 13: 15 (Reel 19)
  - Sikorsky, Igor, 1941; Box/Folder 13: 16 (Reel 19)
  - Simanskaia, L., 1965; Box/Folder 13: 17 (Reel 19)
  - Skriabin, Aleksandr, undated; Box/Folder 13: 18 (Reel 19)
  - Smirnov, Mikhail, 1925-1934; Box/Folder 13: 19 (Reel 19)
  - Sokolov, P. R. and F.(?), 1951-1959; Box/Folder 13: 20 (Reel 19)
  - Sokol'skii, Anatolii A., 1937-1973; Box/Folder 13: 21 (Reel 19)
  - Solomonovskii, Igor', 1971; Box/Folder 13: 22 (Reel 19)
  - Solonevich, Boris Luk'ianovich, 1934-1948.; Box/Folder 13: 23 (Reel 19)
    See also Russian scouting file/Personalia/Solonevich, Boris
  - Solov'ev, Aleksei, 1924-1973; Box/Folder 13: 24 (Reel 19)
  - Somov, Sergei, 1960; Box/Folder 13: 25 (Reel 19)
  - Spiridon, Archimandrite, 1968-1969; Box/Folder 13: 26 (Reel 19)
  - Spiridovich, Nina, undated; Box/Folder 13: 27 (Reel 19)
  - Stadnitska, A., 1964 and undated; Box/Folder 13: 28 (Reel 19)
  - Stakhovich, Aleksei, 1959-1961; Box/Folder 13: 29 (Reel 19)
  - Stashevskii, A. A., 1972 and undated; Box/Folder 13: 30 (Reel 19)
  - Stavrovskii, Aleksei Vladimirovich, 1950-1968; Box/Folder 13: 31 (Reel 19)
  - Stefanovich, Platon, 1969; Box/Folder 13: 32 (Reel 19)
  - Stepanova, E., 1972; Box/Folder 13: 33 (Reel 19)
  - Stevens, Elbert C., Box/Folder 13: 34 (Reel 19)
  - Stogov, Petr E., 1959-1969; Box/Folder 13: 35 (Reel 19)
  - Stogova, Zoia, 1961; Box/Folder 13: 36 (Reel 19)
  - Stoliarov, S. P., Box/Folder 13: 37 (Reel 19)
  - Stupin, Petr Dmitrievich, 1950 and undated; Box/Folder 13: 38 (Reel 19)
  - Suchko, Vladimir, 1972; Box/Folder 13: 39 (Reel 19)
  - Svezhevskii, Boris N., 1948-1969; Box/Folder 13: 40 (Reel 19)
  - Sviechin, Mikhail, 1963-1967; Box/Folder 13: 41 (Reel 19)
  - Tatarina, Vera, 1947-1970; Box/Folder 13: 42 (Reel 19)
  - Tatishchev, D. and E., 1959; Box/Folder 13: 43 (Reel 19)
  - Taube, G. N., 1930; Box/Folder 13: 44 (Reel 19)
  - Temnomerov, Vladimir Apollonovich, 1923-1969 and undated; Box/Folder 13: 45 (Reel 19)
  - Tikhonitskii, Vadim, 1958-1960; Box/Folder 14: 1 (Reel 19)
  - Tizengauzen, N., Baron, 1969; Box/Folder 14: 2 (Reel 19)
  - Tkachenko, N., 1960-1972; Box/Folder 14: 3 (Reel 19)
  - Tkachuk, Igor, Rev., 1951; Box/Folder 14: 4 (Reel 19)
  - Tolstoy Foundation, 1941-1963; Box/Folder 14: 5 (Reel 19)
  - Trankovskii, Pavel Fedorovich, 1965; Box/Folder 14: 6 (Reel 19)
  - Treml, Vladimir, 1950; Box/Folder 14: 7 (Reel 19)
  - Triplo'skii family, 1972; Box/Folder 14: 8 (Reel 19)
  - Trutenko, Lidiia, 1923-1947 and undated; Box/Folder 14: 9 (Reel 19)
  - Tsekh, Dmitrii, 1970 and undated; Box/Folder 14: 10 (Reel 19)
  - Tsolle, Leonid P., 1923; Box/Folder 14: 11 (Reel 19)
  - Tumanskaia, 1961 and undated; Box/Folder 14: 12 (Reel 19)
  - Tuniev, Dimitrii Dimitrievich, 1935; Box/Folder 14: 13 (Reel 19)
  - Ul'man, N., 1918; Box/Folder 14: 14 (Reel 20)
  - Umanskii, Oleg, undated; Box/Folder 14: 15 (Reel 20)
  - Urt'ev, Pavel Andreevich, 1972-1973; Box/Folder 14: 16 (Reel 20)
  - Uvarova, N., 1959-1966; Box/Folder 14: 17 (Reel 20)
  - Vargulevich, S., 1968; Box/Folder 14: 18 (Reel 20)
  - Veideman, Vasilii Gugovich, 1959; Box/Folder 14: 19 (Reel 20)
  - Vekman, 1961; Box/Folder 14: 20 (Reel 20)
  - Vera Konstantinovna, Princess, 1969; Box/Folder 14: 21 (Reel 20)
  - Vertsinskii, E. A., 1929; Box/Folder 14: 22 (Reel 20)
  - Veselovzorov, Boris Petrovich, 1937; Box/Folder 14: 23 (Reel 20)
  - Viazemskaia, Ol'ga, 1961; Box/Folder 14: 24 (Reel 20)
  - Viaz'mitinov, Aleksandr Mikhailovich, 1934-1973; Box/Folder 14: 25 (Reel 20)
  - Viktorin, Hieromonk, 1950; Box/Folder 14: 26 (Reel 20)
  - Vitte, G. K., 1930; Box/Folder 14: 27 (Reel 20)
  - Vladimir, Monk, 1972; Box/Folder 14: 28 (Reel 20)
  - Vladimir Kirillovich, Grand Duke, 1956; Box/Folder 14: 29 (Reel 20)
  - Volchenko, Mariia, 1950-1969; Box/Folder 14: 30 (Reel 20)
  - Vrangel', Petr, 1972; Box/Folder 14: 31 (Reel 20)
  - Walska, Mrs., undated, Box/Folder 14: 32 (Reel 20)
  - Ward, Barbara, 1967; Box/Folder 14: 33 (Reel 20)
  - Zapolenko, Sergei, 1947-1948; Box/Folder 14: 34 (Reel 20)
  - Zarubezhnyi soiuz russkikh voennykh invalidov. Otdel v Frantsii, 1962-1965; Box/Folder 14: 35 (Reel 20)
  - Zavalishin, N., 1927-1929; Box/Folder 14: 36 (Reel 20)
  - Zembulatov, V. and N., 1954-1972 and undated; Box/Folder 14: 37 (Reel 20)
  - Zemskov, P., 1962-1972; Box/Folder 14: 38 (Reel 20)
  - Zemtsova, Nadezhda Petrovna, 1968-1973; Box/Folder 14: 39 (Reel 20)
  - Zhdanov, Boris and N. A., 1972; Box/Folder 14: 40 (Reel 20)
  - Zhigalin, N. A., 1972; Box/Folder 14: 41 (Reel 20)
  - Zhiromskaia, E., 1929; Box/Folder 14: 42 (Reel 20)
  - Zhukov, Gavriil, 1923-1955; Box/Folder 14: 43 (Reel 20)
    For material about Zhukov, see Russian scouting file/Country files/Russia
  - Zhukov, Innokentii, 1922-1923.; Box/Folder 14: 44 (Reel 20)
  - Zhukov, Romil Gavriilovich, 1949-1970 and undated; Box/Folder 14: 45 (Reel 20)
  - Zhukovskii, Anatolii, 1937-1949; Box/Folder 14: 46 (Reel 20)
- Speeches and writings, 1914-1969 and undated; Box/Folder 15-16 (Reel 21-23)
  Holographs, typescripts and printed matter, arranged chronologically by title
  - General, 1935-1962 and undated
    - Drafts and notes, undated
      - General, undated; Box/Folder 15: 1 (Reel 21)
      - General, (contd.), undated; Box/Folder 15: 2 (Reel 22)
      - Military, undated; Box/Folder 15: 3 (Reel 22)
        Includes recollections of the First World War, particular battles and regimental life
      - Poetry, undated; Box/Folder 15: 4 (Reel 22)
      - Scouting, undated; Box/Folder 15: 5 (Reel 22)
    - Letters to the editor, 1935-1962 and undated; Box/Folder 15: 6 (Reel 22)
    - Notebook, 1952-1953; Box/Folder 15: 7 (Reel 22)
    - Obituaries, holograph, typescript and printed copies, undated; Box/Folder 15: 8 (Reel 22)
      Subjects include Konstantin Aleksandrovich Pertsov, Vasilii Vasil'evich Fokht, Sergei Karlovich Geinrikhsen, Tat'iana Vladimirovna Surovtsova, Vladimir Vasil'evich Rudnev, Mariia Nikolaevna Il'ina, Aleksandr Aleksandrovich Petrovskii
  - "Chekhov po ego pis'mam," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 9 (Reel 22)
  - "Kolybel' russkikh skautov," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 10 (Reel 22)
  - "L. gv. Strielkovyi Ego Velichestva batal'ion: kolybel' russkikh skautov-razviedchikov," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 11 (Reel 22)
  - "Lermontov i Rossiia," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 12 (Reel 22)
  - "Molitvennyia i santimental'nyia zapiski," typescript, undated; Box/Folder 15: 13 (Reel 22)
  - "Niu Iork," typescript, undated; Box/Folder 15: 14 (Reel 22)
  - "O sv. Vladimirskoi ikonie Bozh'ei Materi," holograph and typescript, undated; Box/Folder 15: 15 (Reel 22)
  - "Ot Pushkina do Bloka," typescript and holograph supplement, undated; Box/Folder 15: 16 (Reel 22)
  - "Po Floridie," holograph,., undated; Box/Folder 15: 17 (Reel 22)
  - "Russkie skauty (natsional'naia organizatsiia)," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 18 (Reel 22)
  - "Russkie skauty-razviedchiki," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 19 (Reel 22)
  - "Tiflisskii kad. Korpus," holograph, undated; Box/Folder 15: 20 (Reel 22)
  - "Tolstoi i Sevastopol'," Holograph, undated; Box/Folder 16: 1 (Reel 23)
  - Untitled speech for Christmas celebration, holograph, undated; Box/Folder 16: 2 (Reel 23)
  - Untitled writing on child-rearing, holograph, undated; Box/Folder 16: 3 (Reel 23)
  - "Zadachi vospitaniia molodezhi," typescript, undated; Box/Folder 16: 4 (Reel 23)
  - Boi-skauty, printed copy and later typescript, 1914; Box/Folder 16: 5 (Reel 23)
  - "St. George's Day in Soviet Russia," typescript, 1923 June 26; Box/Folder 16: 6 (Reel 23)
  - "O roverakh. Russkim skautam," typescript, 1924 June 14; Box/Folder 16: 7 (Reel 23)
  - "Nashi skauty na Dzhembori," holograph, 1929; Box/Folder 16: 8 (Reel 23)
  - Russkim skautam: prikazy, instruktsii, informatsii i besiedy, printed copy, 1929; Box/Folder 16: 9 (Reel 23)
  - Speeches for Den' russkoi Kul'tury, holograph, 1935 and undated; Box/Folder 16: 10 (Reel 23)
  - Foreword to Russian translation of Robert Baden-Powell's Scouting for Boys, holograph drafts, 1937; Box/Folder 16: 11 (Reel 23)
  - "Opisanie formy i programmy na razriady," typescript, 1937 June 15; Box/Folder 16: 12 (Reel 23)
  - "Iz pisem," holograph and typescript, [1940-1941]; Box/Folder 16: 13 (Reel 23)
  - "K piatidesiatilietiiu russkikh skautov-razviedchikov," holograph, [1959]; Box/Folder 16: 14 (Reel 23)
  - "Piatdesiat let," typescript, [1959]; Box/Folder 16: 15 (Reel 23)
  - "50-lietie," holograph, [1959]; Box/Folder 16: 16 (Reel 23)
  - "Piatidesiatilietie russkikh skautov-razviedchikov," holograph, [1959]; Box/Folder 16: 17 (Reel 23)
  - "Russkie skauty-razvedchiki," printed copy, Rossiia, 1959 May 8; Box/Folder 16: 18 (Reel 23)
  - "Poiezdka vo Florentsiiu," holograph, 1966; Box/Folder 16: 19 (Reel 23)
  - "The Black Anniversary," typescript, 1967; Box/Folder 16: 20 (Reel 23)
    Includes Russian version, entitled "Chernyi god," and associated correspondence
  - "U lukomor'ia dub zelenyi," printed copy, 1968 December 12; Box/Folder 16: 21 (Reel 23)
  - O dniakh bylykh: semeinaia khronika Pantiukhovykh, 1969; Box/Folder 16: (Reel 23)
    - Typescript, undated; Box/Folder 16: 22 (Reel 23)
    - Supplemental notes, holograph, undated; Box/Folder 16: 23 (Reel 23)
    - Reviews, 1969; Box/Folder 16: 24 (Reel 23)
  - "Russkim skautam-razvedchikam ko dniu 60-letiia 20 aprelia 1969 goda," printed copy and holograph drafts, Novoe russkoe slovo, 1969 April 25; Box/Folder 16: 25 (Reel 23)
- Russian scouting file, 1910-1989 and undated; Box 17-25 (Reel 24-39)
  Artwork, awards, bylaws, clippings, country file, instructions, lists, orders, personalia file, promotional materials, reports, printed matter, songs and poems, writings, arranged alphabetically by physical form and chronologically therein
  - General, 1921-1974
    - ORIuR-NORS unification, 1953-1975 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 1 (Reel 24)
    - Relations with foreign and international scouting organizations
      - General, 1922-1984 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 2 (Reel 24)
      - Boy Scouts International Bureau, 1921-1953.; Box/Folder 17: 3 (Reel 24)
        Includes correspondence with Sir Robert-Baden-Powell (mainly copies of outgoing letters)
      - Boy Scouts of America, 1922-1974 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 4 (Reel 24)
      - Girl Guides/Girl Scouts, 1927-1938 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 5 (Reel 24)
      - "Tragediia Rossii,", 1950-1987; Box/Folder 17: 6 (Reel 24)
      - Welfare Committee for the Russian Boy Scouts Abroad, 1929-1931.; Box/Folder 17: 7 (Reel 25)
        See also Correspondence/Bristol, Warren
  - Artwork and illustrations, undated; Box/Folder 17: 8 (Reel 25)
  - Awards, 1935-1973 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 9 (Reel 25)
  - Bylaws, 1952-1966 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 10 (Reel 25)
  - Clippings, 1923-1989 and undated; Box/Folder 17: 11 (Reel 25)
  - Country files, 1918-1983
    - Algeria, undated, Box/Folder 18: 1 (Reel 26)
    - Argentina, 1935-1972; Box/Folder 18: 2 (Reel 26)
    - Australia, 1954-1975; Box/Folder 18: 3 (Reel 26)
    - Austria, 1948; Box/Folder 18: 4 (Reel 26)
    - Belgium, 1922-1964; Box/Folder 18: 5 (Reel 26)
    - Brazil, 1931-1946; Box/Folder 18: 6 (Reel 26)
    - Bulgaria, 1922-1940; Box/Folder 18: 7 (Reel 26)
    - Chile, 1951; Box/Folder 18: 8 (Reel 27)
    - China
      - General, orders, 1923-1940; Box/Folder 18: 9 (Reel 27)
      - Undated, Box/Folder 18: 10 (Reel 27)
      - 1920-1929, Box/Folder 18: 11 (Reel 27)
      - 1930-1934, Box/Folder 19: 1 (Reel 28)
      - 1935-1939, Box/Folder 19: 2 (Reel 28)
      - 1940-1948, Box/Folder 19: 3 (Reel 29)
    - Czechoslovakia, 1922-1935; Box/Folder 19: 4 (Reel 29)
    - Egypt, 1936-1945; Box/Folder 19: 5 (Reel 29)
    - England, 1922-1940; Box/Folder 19: 6 (Reel 29)
    - Estonia, 1922-1940; Box/Folder 20: 1 (Reel 29)
    - Finland, 1922-1944; Box/Folder 20: 2 (Reel 30)
    - France
      - 1920-1924 and undated, Box/Folder 20: 3 (Reel 30)
      - 1925-1929, Box/Folder 20: 4 (Reel 31)
      - 1930-1939, Box/Folder 21: 1 (Reel 31)
      - 1940-1972, Box/Folder 21: 2 (Reel 32)
    - Germany, 1922-1959; Box/Folder 21: 3 (Reel 32)
    - Greece, 1922-1940; Box/Folder 21: 4 (Reel 33)
    - Hungary, 1933-1939; Box/Folder 21: 5 (Reel 33)
    - Italy, 1923-1935; Box/Folder 22: 1 (Reel 33)
    - Latvia
      - 1922-1935, Box/Folder 22: 2 (Reel 33)
      - 1936-1940, Box/Folder 22: 3 (Reel 33)
    - Lebanon, 1936; Box/Folder 22: 4 (Reel 33)
    - Lithuania, 1922-1938; Box/Folder 22: 5 (Reel 33)
    - Morocco, 1949-1950; Box/Folder 22: 6 (Reel 33)
    - Philippines (Tubabao), 1949-1951; Box/Folder 22: 7 (Reel 34)
    - Poland, 1922-1947; Box/Folder 22: 8 (Reel 34)
    - Romania, 1929; Box/Folder 23: 1 (Reel 35)
    - Russia, 1917-1932 and undated; Box/Folder 23: 2 (Reel 35)
    - Syria, 1925; Box/Folder 23: 3 (Reel 35)
    - Tunisia, 1922; Box/Folder 23: 4 (Reel 35)
    - Turkey, 1920-1923; Box/Folder 23: 5 (Reel 35)
    - United States
      - 1929-1969 and undated, Box/Folder 23: 6 (Reel 35)
      - 1970-1983, Box/Folder 23: 7 (Reel 35)
    - Uruguay, 1935; Box/Folder 23: 8 (Reel 35)
    - Yugoslavia
      - 1920-1929 and undated, Box/Folder 23: 9 (Reel 36)
      - 1930-1939, Box/Folder 24: 1 (Reel 36)
      - 1940-1941, Box/Folder 24: 2 (Reel 36)
  - Instructions and rules, undated; Box/Folder 24: 3 (Reel 37)
  - Lists and rosters, undated; Box/Folder 24: 4 (Reel 37)
  - Orders and talks ("Prikazy i besedy"), 1922-1980 and undated; Box/Folder 24: 5 (Reel 37)
  - Personalia file, 1920-1986
    - Gardner, Ivan Alekseevich, 1921-1923; Box/Folder 24: 6 (Reel 37)
    - Piterskii, Evgenii Sergeevich, 1986; Box/Folder 24: 7 (Reel 37)
    - Preobrazhenskii, Vasilii Sergeevich, undated; Box/Folder 24: 8 (Reel 37)
    - Prokhorov, Konstantin N., 1937; Box/Folder 24: 9 (Reel 37)
    - Radetskii-Mikulich, Georgii Vasil'evich and Vasilii Pavlovich, 1943 and undated; Box/Folder 24: 10 (Reel 37)
    - Sergievskii, Boris Vasil'evich, undated; Box/Folder 24: 11 (Reel 37)
    - Solonevich, Boris Luk'ianovich, 1920-1972 and undated; Box/Folder 24: 12 (Reel 37)
    - Temnomerov, Vladimir Apollonovich, 1920-1978 and undated; Box/Folder 24: 13 (Reel 37)
  - Promotional material, undated; Box/Folder 24: 14 (Reel 37)
  - Religious material, undated; Box/Folder 24: 15 (Reel 37)
  - Reports, 1960-1983; Box/Folder 25: 1 (Reel 38)
  - Songs and poems, 1917-1966 and undated; Box/Folder 25: 2 (Reel 38)
  - Writings, 1929-1989 and undated.; Box/Folder 25: 3 (Reel 38)
    Includes writings by various authors on the history, philosophy and methodology of scouting. See also Oversize file/Writings
  - Printed matter